[
    {
    "question": "1 What is the color Red?",
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "possibleAnswers": ["one","Blue", "Red", "Green", "Yellow"]
},
{
    "question": "2 What is the color Blue?",
    "correctAnswer": "Blue",
    "possibleAnswers": ["two","Blue", "Green", "Red", "Black"]
}, 
{
    "question": "3 What is the color Yellow?",
    "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
    "possibleAnswers": ["three","Blue", "Red", "Green", "Yellow"]
},
{
    "question": "4 What is the color Green?",
    "correctAnswer": "Green",
    "possibleAnswers": ["four","Blue", "Red", "Green", "Yellow"]
},
{
    "question": "5 What is the color Pink?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pink",
    "possibleAnswers": ["five","Blue", "Red", "Green", "Yellow"]
},
{
    "question": "6 What is the color Purple?",
    "correctAnswer": "Purple",
    "possibleAnswers": ["six","Pink", "Purple", "Orange", "White"]
},
{
    "question": "7 What is the color Orange?",
    "correctAnswer": "Orange",
    "possibleAnswers": ["seven","Pink", "Purple", "Orange", "White"]
},
{
    "question": "8 What is the color Black?",
    "correctAnswer": "Black",
    "possibleAnswers": ["eight","Pink", "Black", "Orange", "White"]
},
{
    "question": "9 What is the color Gray?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gray",
    "possibleAnswers": ["nine","Pink", "Gray", "Black", "White"]
},
{
    "question": "10 What is the color Magenta?",
    "correctAnswer": "Magenta",
    "possibleAnswers": ["ten","Pink", "Purple", "Magenta", "White"]
}
]
